CONTACI

- +91 7339671282
- ✓ vidhyashakthi09@gmail.com
- 123 ,Ayesha flats,Ganga St,Vadapalani, Chennai.

EDUCATION

2017-2021

ARIYALUR ENGINEERING COLLEGE

 BE- Electrical and Electronics Engineering
GPA: 7.8 / 10

CERTIFICATION

Web Developement - HEJEX TECHNOLOGY

WEB TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- MySQL

FRAMEWORKS

- Django
- Flask

SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Team Player

VIDHYA S

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

With 2 years of experience as a Software Engineer at VirtualaMaze Sofsys Private Limited, I have successfully delivered major projects and managed CRs, resulting in a 30% increase in usersatisfaction. I excel at creating visually appealing and user-friendly websites. In just 2 years, I have proven myself as a skilled

and efficient team member.

WORK EXPERIENCE(2 YEARS)

 VirtualMaze Sofsys Pvt Lmt Software Engineer JUNE 2022 - DEC 2023

- Successfully delivered major projects and managed Change Requests (CRs), resulting in a 30% increase in user satisfaction.
- Excelled at creating visually appealing and user-friendly websites. Proven track record as a skilled and efficient team member.
- Aequalis Software Solution Pvt Lmt

Jan 2022 - June 2022

Python Developer - Internship

 I started at Aequalis Software Solution in 2022 as new graduate hire, in the years following I worked major deliveries and CR management projects.

PROJECTS

NOT - Namma Ooru Taxi(Taxi Booking and Location Tracking)

An office ride booking and management application for corporate companies and managing ride services.

The tech of the application includes Python-Flask(logic's,API),MySQL.Invlove RESTful API's and creating schema's.

GPS Tool

It is a very useful for any kind of travellers and the people who depend on GPS and related utilities.

Nowadays most of the time we need to know about our current GPS location & its address, weather, forecast, air quality, vehicle speed, satellite signal strengths, GPS alarm and more.

SDAT - Sports Registration Portal

A sports registration portal developed using Python(Django) is a web application designed to streamline the process of registering participants for sports events. The tech of the application includes Python-Django